[{"answer": "You want somethin'", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Nope.  my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You my friend", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "my friend around", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "It's your radiator hose.  It's busted", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Well, you know so much why don't you just fix it yourself", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah, I can fix it.  Gotta run over to the yard and see if I can find a hose like this one, or close enough. Gonna take time", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Time", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "How much time", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " What time is it now", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Accident", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, right.  Someplace in this dust bowl I can get something to drink", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah I want something.  I want you to run over to that machine and get me a pop", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Hell no, I can't do that myself. I'm blind.  Can't you see that", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You can't do that yourself", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'm sorry, I didn'", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, I didn'", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't know.  I thought you were keeping the sun from your eyes", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Do you have to call me that", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Maybe I don't want you to", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " That a fact", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Yes, I have", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You don't have that dead look in your eyes like the only thing you live for is to get through the day", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Drove into Sierra?  What for", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What happens if you lose", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " Somewhere else.  I've never been anywhere else.  Just once.  Years ago.  Went to the state fair.  It was nice, but it wasn't nothing", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "That's good.  Cools you right off.  I saw you watching me", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I didn't say it bothered me", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I'm sorry.  I didn't mean to", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Did you like i", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Like they're made of polyester", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Nothing like a little liveliness", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Who the hell are you", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Husband . . .", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I guess we've never been introduced proper.  my friend", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I'm a solid man", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "That's all right.  He doesn't want to give me the pack . . ", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "You don't know the how, Mr. my friend. And that's not the half of it.  I've got your money, and I go into this little grocery store to get something to eat and it gets robbed", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No.  He gets shot by the old lady", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What happened to your hand", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Got any requests", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I wasn't doing anything", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Make time?  Is everybody in this town slap happy", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What was that all about", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "More like my friend is after every man she sees", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I was hoping we could talk", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "About things.  About your wife", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "This morning I didn't know how badly I'd want to get out of this fucking town", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "For that I'd kill a nun on Easter Sunday", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "You drive a hard bargain, but I had a feeling you were my boy when I met you", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Don't say that.  I had a marriage of convenience with my friend, and look where that's lead.  Well, looks like we got ourselves a pact", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "What should I do", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "You want to do this yourself?  I don't have to do this, you know", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I can't", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Grace, I can't.  I can't even get out of here myself.  I need a hundre", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Please.  I won't hang on you.  As soon as we get there you can dump me.  I don't care.  I just want to get out of here", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I know where we could get the money. A lot more than on", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "He doesn't give it to us.  We take it", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "I hate to bust your bubble, but I wasn't defending you", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "I wasn't going to fight for you.  I was just going to beat the shit out of your boyfriend", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "How old are you", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "No, I don't want to take you for a ride.  What I want is for . . . Hey, you don't happen to have a hundred and fifty dollars I coul", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "You said this morning the hose was going to run me on", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "It's going to cost you tw", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Yep.  For the hose.  But while you was gone I replaced a gasket. That's going to run you another fifty", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "How much", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": " One way", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Get up, Mister!  Don't ever let it be said my friend beat the living shit out of someone without giving them a fair chance", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "I'm doing what any man would do if he'd been offended.  I'm beating you up", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "More or less", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "We all got plans.  I planned on seeing all my life.  I know you didn't plan on straying into town", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Not this twig, friend.  I got plans", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "No and I don't plan on sticking around either.  I don't guess I'll be seeing you again.  Take it easy", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "There's someone in the house", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "The wind isn't blowing", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "There's another reason?  It better be good", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "You came to take my wife from me", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "You're not talking sense", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "What are you . . . you can't . . . you can't kill me", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "A drifter, a loner, a trouble maker like you?  Just passing through town, need money so he busts in on an, old man.  Only this old man's got himself an automatic, and he knows how to use it.  A man's got to protect his home.  His wife.  You're dead, boy, and your own mother wouldn't convict me", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "You're right.  I don't give a damn about her.  But to fuck a man's wife behind his back?  That just makes a fool out of him.  I don't like being made a fool of", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "What difference does it make if I slept with her.  You don't care about Grace", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "I don't blame you.  What man would? I admit it, okay?  I came back here and I made it with Grace.  But if you kill me you're making a big mistake", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "Just cool down, son.  I ain't accusing you of anything.  Serves Toby right to get his ass whooped. If you hadn't done it, somebody else would've", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "Nope.  No problems up the road", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "Walk to where?  We're fifty miles to the nearest town.  It's going to be over on", "docId": "u-turn_early.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "Yeah, they'll find you.  Dried up and twice dead", "qsentId": 90}]